

**Address** Baguiati Kolkata, Pin: 700159

#### Contact

+91 9635803795/7872467430 atanudeb17@gmail.com

**Date of Birth** 17.06.1994

# **PROFILE**

Total 3+ years of experience in SAP ABAP & ABAP ON HANA development (S/4 HANA 1709,1809,1909). Presently working as SAP tech. developer at IBM for the SAP-ABAP ON S/4 HANA implementation project which covers development and customization of ABAP applications and Performance management, defining the technical solution, integration solution, development standards, design and development of interfaces to third party systems. Provided solutions for their complex business scenarios. Specialties: WRICEFs, ABAP with OOPS, DDIC Objects, User exits, Enhancement, Web Services(WSDL), SAP HR module, SAP S4 HANA MIGRATION COCKPIT (LTMC & LTMOM), OData, eCATT, implement notes. I have worked on three SAP S/4 HANA greenfield and brownfield implementation projects.

## **SKILLS**

- ✓ CORE ABAP
- ✓ 00 ABAP
- Cross Application ABAP
- ✓ ABAP on HANA
- ✓ S/4 HANA Migration Cockpit
- ✓ CDS Views, AMDP, OData

### **EDUCATION**

08.2013 - 07.2017

**Jalpaiguri Government Engineering College**B. Tech in Information Technology, DGPA: 9.22

# CERTIFICATION

- SAP Certified Development Specialist ABAP for SAP HANA 2.0
- AZ-900, AI-900, DP-900

### LANGUAGES

# **PERSONALITY**

- ✓ Punctuality
- ✓ Creativity
- ✓ Organized

# ATANU DEB

SAP ABAP on HANA Consultant



Linkedin

http://linkedin.com/in/atanu-deb-170694/

#### **EXPERIENCE**

04.2018 - present IBM India Pvt. Ltd.

Designation: SAP ABAP on HANA Consultant

**Project:** INEOS USA LLC - S4 HANA 1909 ( **Duration**: AUG-2020 to Present)

Role: SAP ABAP HANA Consultant

- Develop things from scratch like reports, tables, interfaces, classes, and many more. Working independently and helping in designing parts too.
- Worked on many process areas in this project such as OTC, Logistics, MFG, EAM, Cross application, Conversion, SAP Workday HR (OM-PM integration), etc, and developed Interfaces, Enhancements in OO ABAP concept
- Worked in S4 HANA MIGRATION COCKPIT (LTMC, LTMOM for both standard and custom objects).
- IDOCs
- Adobe forms
- Use Analysis for office, Query Browser for report analysis
- LSMW, BDC, eCATT to load/update data in mass mode.
- $\bullet$  Development of conversion programs for SD, MM, FI, PM transactions
- Worked on CDS (with VDM, DCL), AMDP.
- Worked in O Data.
- Actively extract and load production data before Go Live.

**Project**: Elanco Animal Health SAP S/4 HANA Implementation 1809 ( **Duration**: JAN-2020 to JUL-2020)

Role: SAP ABAP HANA Consultant

- Worked on many process areas such as Logistics, MFG, QM, IBP, Sales and Distribution (OTC), etc.
- Developed Interfaces, Enhancements, Web services (WSDL) based on ABAP 7.5 latest syntaxes, OO concept.
- Provide the ABAP solution wherever required according to the user requirements.
- · Bug fixing.
- Recommending the best solution for the problem to the client.

**Project**: HAVI Logistics S/4 HANA 1709 Greenfield implementation ( **Duration**: NOV-2018 to DEC-2019)

Role: SAP ABAP Consultant

- WRICEF objects (Report, enhancement, AMDP, DDIC Objects) using ABAP 7.5 new syntaxes and OO Concept within deadline with proper documentation as per FS.
- Understanding of reports, enhancements, etc preparing technical specs according to functional specs.
- Developed ALV reports and custom function modules. Understand the end-user requirement, participating in individual meetings
- Ensure the quality of deliverables.